http://www.lfw.co.uk/privacy-policy

Menu
Christmas & GiftsGiftsChristmasAdvent CalendarsPersonalised WhiskyGin & Other SpiritsGift SetsGift CardsAccessoriesSpecial Years18 Years20 Years21 Years25 Years30 Years40 Years50 Years1970198019901995199920002002Gift IdeasThe Loch FyneWhisky Gift PackThe Loch FyneGin & Liqueur Taster PackNewSaleThe Loch Fyne RangeOur BrandsThe Loch Fyne RangeThe Living CaskThe Loch Fyne Single CasksThe Loch Fyne BlendThe Loch Fyne LiqueursThe Loch Fyne GinThe Loch Fyne Gift PacksThe Loch Fyne Range The Loch Fyne BlendThe Living Cask 1745The Loch Fyne Botanical GinScotch WhiskyScotch WhiskySingle Malt WhiskySpeysideIslayIslandHighlandLowlandCampbeltownExclusivesLimited EditionsSingle Cask WhiskyBlended WhiskyGrain WhiskyFlavour MapFlavour MapLight & SmokyRich & SmokyLight & DelicateRich & DelicateShop By BrandTaliskerMacallanGlenfiddichGlenDronachArdbegBalvenieAberlourBunnahabhainLaphroaigBruichladdichKilchomanBrands A-ZFeatured Scotch WhiskyArranSherry CaskThe BodegaWorld WhiskyRegionsJapanese WhiskyIrish WhiskeyAmerican WhiskeyRest of WorldShop By BrandHakushuHibikiYamazakiNikkaJack Daniel'sMaker's MarkOld ForesterJamesonRedbreastTullamore DewThe Lakes DistilleryBrands A-ZFeatured World WhiskyGreen SpotHibiki 17 Year OldCollector's Loft
Account
Settings
Currency
GBP (£)
EUR (€)
JPY (¥)
TWD (NT$)
USD ($)
We Ship Worldwide
Free UK Delivery over £75
Fyne Tuned Whisky Knowledge
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Loch Fyne Whiskies is committed to ensuring that your personal information is secure. We will not disclose your information to third parties other than when order details are processed as part of the order fulfilment and delivery process or unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
Data collected by this site is used:
To take and fulfil customer orders
For internal record keeping and to monitor customer account status beyond that required for individual purchases
To issue a unique identifier (e.g. customer login)
On occasion, we may use your information to contact you by email, phone or mail for market research purposes. We may use the information to administer and enhance the site and service.
By registering as a Loch Fyne customer, you are consenting to the collection of your personal data.
If you have agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at info@lochfynewhiskies.com or by writing to us at Loch Fyne Whiskies, Main Street, Inveraray, Argyll, PA32 8UD.
Under the Data Protection Act 1998, you may ask for details of any personal information that we hold about you. To do so, you should contact us either by email of in writing as above. If you find any inaccuracies we will correct it promptly.
Or you can do this through the website. After logging into the site, your personal information will be made available for review and change in the "My Account" section. Only you may access your personal data from the website using your User ID and password. You can change personal information on the website within Account Information and My details section. If you prefer, you may contact us by email at info@lochfynewhiskies.com and, at your request, we will amend your personal details.
Cookies are used on this shopping site where they are strictly necessary for the site functionality. They are used to aid navigation, and to keep track of the contents of your shopping cart. If you log in to an account, your logged-in status is recorded in a temporary cookie. If you select the 'Remember Me' option in the checkout, a cookie will be used to remember your details. You can turn off cookies by blocking them in your browser Privacy settings. If you turn off cookies, you may be prevented from taking advantage of the features in the website that use them.
About UsAbout UsOur PeopleLocationsHistoryHamish's BlogWhisky GuideCustomer ServiceContact UsDeliveryFAQsSell Your WhiskyAffiliatesPrivacyTerms and Conditions
